Suddenly Explorers! Suddenly Explorers! Explorers out of the blue!
Next, this star knight on the right! It's the Suddenly Explorers! Please help me out!
Get out of the way!
Let's go!
Yes!
Yes! We're here to explore!
Wait a minute! What? Is this room full of helium gas?
No!
Yes, this is the Ikinari Expedition. Hello. Today I would like to talk to you both.
I would like to ask you two, are you tired these days? Yes, I am!
You seem to be very full of energy. Seriously, I am very tired. I have prepared this project for you two.
Let's get energized at Genki Michi Oriki Oekonin on the 3rd floor of E-Beans!
Genki!
Do you know the Genki Michi Orikiin on the 3rd floor of E-Beans?
We are going there today to take care of your tired bodies.
What a treat! That's a reward!
I'm just a little stiff. I was on an expedition yesterday.
What exactly will be done is pelvic correction!
You've seen it before, right? You've seen the "before and after" type of things. You have seen the person who had such bad posture, and now, wow!
You see it in the line-up?
You can actually experience that, and if you have any specific pain here on your body, or if you have any pinpoint problems, you can ask us about them.
Let's go to Genki Michi today and feel better! Let's move on to the store! Let's go!
At E-WINDS 3 times Genki Michi Seikatsu Committee, we are going to improve the root of those painful symptoms that don't improve no matter where you go!
Healthy ecology starting from the pelvis, and needles to improve your immune system!
First time discount campaign is also available!
Please tell us you saw our website when you make an appointment!
Today, I am Mr. Ishioka and Ms. Shimbo, thank you for your help. Nice to meet you.
Today, we are going to have a two-person pelvic osteopathy session, so one of you will be doing pelvic osteopathy, and the other will be consulting about your body problems.
Do you have a quick glance as to which pelvic osteopathy is better suited or which is better to do?
At a glance, it's hard to tell.
It's not clear?
Yes. Let's have him lie down on his face.
I see. First of all, you want to see if there is a gap.
I'll go first.
Then, let's start with you.
First of all, when you put your legs together, you can see the length of your pelvis here, and if this is not aligned with your left or right, it is considered to be misaligned.
In other words, if the pelvis is misaligned in this way or that way, it looks like it is misaligned.
You look strange.
Me too.
Now I see that there is no misalignment between the left and right sides of the body.
That's right.
If you look at it this way, I don't think it will look like this, so I'm fine.
So it's not that far off?
Not that much.
Wow. That's good.
This one doesn't have it, but the ones before and after may have it.
I don't see anything like this one, but this one. There might be a before and after of this one.
But it was good.
I think it's not that bad.
I see.
Okay, I'll take a look.
Yes.
May I ask you to put it on for a moment?
This side is...
Isn't this side a little short?
Short! Yes, it is!
Really short!
I didn't do anything to it.
This side is a little shorter.
Really short!
It's totally different!
Do you have one of these on your desk?
Yes, yes, yes!
This one is a little off.
Your pelvis is like this.
It's distorted.
So we need to move it back a little bit.
It's no good.
Yuna, you're not 20 yet.
I've started drinking.
Does it have anything to do with alcohol?
It doesn't have anything to do with drinking.
But the way you cross your legs when you're drinking...
When you do that...
When you're standing, you're always on one side.
I cross my legs a lot.
My friends say that's why people are scared of you.
That's why they're scared of you.
Ah!
I don't know...
Like React.
So, in case you're wondering...
The pelvis is done by Ms. Hazuki.
You mean you're going to do it, right?
Yes, sir.
Then, Mr. Shinbo...
Please do it.
You look like udon noodles.
I'm not sleeping.
Are you feeling all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
If it's too strong or too weak?
But I'm just fine.
Yes, sir.
Isn't this too surreal?
Very surreal.
Is it tight?
I'm pressing right where you're pressing right now. And since you said you wanted to cross your legs...
Do you want it on the top right? That's right!
Correct! Oh, no! Shall I be quiet?Correct! Oh, no! Let's keep it down.
Too scary.
It's definitely messy.
It's definitely not.
It's settled.
I knew it was totally different.
It's totally different.
They're doing something a little weird.
While Ke Kyuna-san was in surgery.
Ippanshi-san's body, like, "I have a pain here..." or something like that.
Let's ask her to consult with us about her problems.
I wonder if it's really the neck or the muscles here.
I have a real pain in my neck, here, and shoulder.
What should I do?
First of all, the cause of stiffness is poor blood flow.
For example, in a season like this, it suddenly gets cold.
For example, in October, it can still be a little warm, can't it?
But when it suddenly gets cold, blood flow becomes poor.
So the first thing to do is simply to warm up the body.
By healing the blood flow, good blood will flow to the place where muscles are in a bad condition.
Blood has the power to heal bad places.
If the blood flow is bad, it will remain bad for a long time.
Therefore, the first thing you can do for yourself is to warm up your muscles.
I think it is better to be thorough in this area.
Do you take a proper bath?
I do take a bath.
Or just take a shower?
Just showers.
That's it.
You mean you use it for steam?
I use the steam.
And then I relax it.
Is it OK if I do it by myself?
If you do it by yourself, you may damage it unexpectedly.
It is better to have a professional staff member do it for you.
I used to put a sticky tape on the stiff area.
But it gets cold every day, doesn't it?
What do you think about that?
If you have a weak skin, it would probably have the opposite effect.
If you have itchy skin or something like that, it would be better not to apply a bandage.
If you have itchy skin, it is better not to use a medical tape.
Warm towel?
A hot-sheet is still better.
They cool down the skin.
Of course, the ingredients of the medicine in the stick can relieve stiffness, but it is better not to use it if you have a rash.
But if you have a rash or something like that, I don't think you need to force it on.
If you are going to put it on, a warm sore is more acceptable.
Is there anything to put on it?
I'm an itchy person.
I thought itching was just a sign of being spoiled, so I just put up with it.
Stiffness can also be caused by stress.
I see. That's absolutely true.
If you are itching, it can also cause stiffness.
I don't want to do too much damage to my body.
I see.
Are you stressed out?
I am stressed out!
Yes, I am.
Yes, I am very stressed out.
Like, "I didn't get a hit today.
I know I'm not going to get any traction.
I've been using a method where I don't look at the audience when I'm telling a story.
You are an idol, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
Do you know if you're not popular? You think about it, don't you?
Yes, I think about it. That's all I think about.
Not about your performance?
I do think about performance.
If mass is a 5, then for comedy it's about an 8.
Why is that?
The other two are about sleeping.
Can I tell you something else?
I'm obsessed with staying alive.
I need to know how to stop being obsessed.
You're our expert.
It's easier to live with stubbornness.
You know, like if you just push the right buttons.
I'm asking as a human being.
Is that a good example?
Why is Nishio-san's example a bad one?
Is it a bad example?
I don't know
I can't say.
I believe you.
I do believe.
It's just that we're the experts now.
We have to go to an exorcism.
Mr. Fujii.
When you were working on it...
You were talking about your neck.
It's really stiff.
I'll have you do a little work on my neck.
Are you sure?
How hard?
Just right.
When you put your head in, you get tired, don't you?
But you don't put your head in there.
You'll drown.
How can I do that?
I'm tired all the way down to my neck.I get tired all the way to my neck.
If I get tired all the way up to my neck.
Drowning?
You don't drown?
I don't drown.
You didn't say, "Stay warm when you're tired.
If your body is tired, the warmth will spread to the whole body.
Actually, you can go as far as this.
I'd be happy if you could do something that makes you tired.
You don't have to come this far.
When I go in with my mom...
When you go in with your mother?
Sometimes with my mom.
Still?
I mean, still... still...
Nah.
You get along well with her?
We may be close.
Do you take a bath with your mother?
No, I don't.
How old were you when you took a bath?
Maybe in the first grade.
First grade?
Once I entered elementary school, I probably stopped taking baths with my mother.
I see.
But you take a bath with your girlfriend, don't you?
No, I don't.
You answered quickly.
I was a bit preoccupied.
I was a bit of a chewer.
You were looking at the camera.
That's embarrassing.
Something must have happened.
It's very elaborate.
Yes, it's very stiff.
It's hard, like I rubbed it.
That's where it's really stiff.
When the base of the neck gets stiff...
Tilt your neck forward or backward.
Bring it back.
This movement becomes difficult.
If you can loosen this part, it's much easier around the neck.
It's so warm right now.
Do you mind if I don't take a bath?
Yes, I do.
Every day, for God's sake.
I will.
Okay, can I ask you a question?
We're finishing up now.
That's what they said.
What would you like to eat?
Ramen. Jiro type.
I see.
With a lot of bean sprouts and stuff.
Jiro-style ramen is delicious, but
But if you eat too much
It's bad for blood flow.
Of course, if you eat too much, it depends on what you eat.
That's true. That's what I meant just now.
But, you know, those contain a lot of oil, don't they?
Yes, yes.
Blood flow is certainly not bad.
I see.
That's why I don't like to eat Jiro-style food.
It's not really good, is it?
Actually, it's not good.
It was over, wasn't it?
It was over before I knew it.
It's amazing.
It's amazing. It's light.
So light.
There wasn't a single animal.
He wasn't that energetic. The two of them.
It's amazing.
It's really amazing.
Are you feeling lighter now?
I feel lighter. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Maybe you are correcting my pelvis.
I feel pain all over my body.
Do you mean you can feel the pain when you have the whole body done?
How is it? My body.
You almost hit me.
I'm sorry.
I was crying.
My body. Not only the left-right distortion you just mentioned, but maybe a warped back is in there as well.
Is there a roll in there? Here.
It's not bad yet.
But my ears.
If the earth were to end right now, what would you eat?
Hip style.
Hamburgers.
Cute.
Where do you get your hamburgers?
What kind?
Mom's.
Cute.
The child's.
Can you do more than just shoe board bodywork?
I'm coming.
Do you do neck and hand work?Can you do my neck and hands?
Yes, we do.
Hand massage is included.
Is that an option?
Yes, it's optional.
That's a little rough.
It's a service.
Of course it is.
Oh! So crispy.
Look at you.
Oh, my God, look at you. Did you open up your hair?
More hair? Definitely more hair.
More hair. More hair volume. Hair volume compulsion.
I see what you mean. That's great. I want to force my hair too.
That's too funny.
I'm done. I'm done. I'm done.
We're done. We're done.
How was it? Actually...
I could tell by the way he pressed on me that I was stiff.
But it wasn't uncomfortable at all.
But it wasn't unpleasant pain at all.
It was like she was pressing on me.
It felt good, and the pain was really effective.
Thank you very much for the reward plan!
Do you see it when I run my feet?
Yes, I do.
Let's see what happens now, shall we?
It was way off before.
It was way off.
Like a capture.
Oh, my God, it's like a one-notta.
Oh?
Oh, no?
Oh! They're all together.
They're all here.
The red and the red are together.
Here and here are attached.
They're the same length.
Oh! It's all there!
That's great!
Look!
That's our hamburger master!
No, no, no. You look like a hamburger master.
Hamburgers!
That's great!
It's all coming together like this.
Wow!
He doesn't know that his pelvis is misaligned, but...
He loosened up the other parts of my body too.
He was a god hand!
Yes, I thought so too.
I've been to many places.
Yes, don't come here.
He was a god hand.
Yes, it was.
It felt so good.
Stand up, the view is different.
I understand.
And, and, and, and, and...
Bye, bye, bye.
What are you doing?
It's the best view I've ever had.
I've never seen anything like it.
Even my eyesight is better
My eyes are open.
It's amazing.
Four in a row.
Black and pink!
What are you doing? Don't make me do anything crazy! I'm sorry.
Well then, we've finished with the two of you.
How was it, Ms. Fujitani? Counseling on your problems
I learned that it's good to keep your hands warm.
and warming them up.
I feel so much lighter.
It goes wherever it wants to go.
I was doing this in the morning.
I could only turn this far.
Now I can turn this far.
Can I ask you to say something?
I'm sorry, ever.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Fujitani.
I don't know if you can see...
The length of your legs...
They were really out of alignment, but now they're in alignment.
It's hard to walk, isn't it?
But you corrected my pelvis in the first place.
I've also had a lot of work done on my neck and shoulders.
neck and shoulder area, and other things.
I'm feeling more powerful.
I feel like my hands are higher.
I feel my posture is better.
When I did this, my hands became higher.
This is how it naturally happens.
It's not like this, it's like this.
Did you do that?
That's how effective it was.
Let me thank you again.
Okay.Seino
Thank you very much.
This is Genki-Do.
If you have any advertisement or announcement
I'd like to receive it here.
We have a lot.
You don't have to drink it.
By the way, this pelvic osteopathy
Normally, it costs 4,950 yen.
If you watch this video, you can receive it for only 3,850 yen!
Held in 2022
That's great!
Is there a time frame?
Let's do it by the end of the year.
Within the year!
2022.
So the people who came to our show
They'll say they're tired of the show.
Keep it up.
Does this mean when you make a reservation?
You don't have to make a reservation.
It just won't go as smoothly if you do.
I'll put on another play.
Discount on TVZ's YouTube page.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much!
I hope you will all enjoy this high quality of life.
It's God's love.
It really is God's love!
If you are tired from work, or if you are funny, or if you are tired from work, or if you are tired from work...
And all the funny people...
I am cheering for you!
That's all for today's exploration.
Thank you very much.
See you at Unions, Black Pink.
See you soon.
Bye-bye.